(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T20:44:02.664547",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Crazyになるほど恋している ZOMBIE
Crazy in Love ZOMBIE
HOLOLIVE INDONESIA SECOND GENERATION
KUREIJI OLLIE PRESENT
KUREIJI OLLIE PRESENTS
Crazyになるほど恋している ZOMBIE
Crazy in Love ZOMBIE
キミのびっくりした顔、ほんっとにかわいいね～♪
Your startled face is so cute~
これって、ずーっと楽しみにしてたんじゃないの～？
Wasn't this what you were waiting for~?
だって、推しと直接お話できるんだよ～？
To be able to talk to your oshi~
あれれ～？なんで戻るボタンなんか何回も押してるの～？
Hmm, why the frantic button pressing dear?
もしかして……オリーこうやってお話しするの、イヤだったのかな～？
Don't tell me you actually dislike this kind of interaction~
え～っ？なんでスマホの電源切っちゃうの～？
Aww, why'd you turn off the phone?
キミってさ……オリーと話すの、ほんとにイヤだったんだ～？
You really don't want to talk to me huh~
楽しみはすぐにはじまるから～！
The fun is just about to begin~!
ダーリ～ン
Darling~
存在証明 愛だって 愛だって 吐いたって 鳴呼
Proof of my existence, "it's romance," I say and still
寝転んゴロンでニャンニャン プリティプリティ ダイエットDAY
Prettily, prettily, dieting DAY
曖昧二回楽に アイマイミ―快楽に
Rough love in secret, my not-safe-for-work goodbye
病み悪化してんだって 愛だ恋だ何だってんだ
Obsessive actions, my dancing, putrefaction, ah
生命線は 愛だって 愛だって 投げたって 鳴呼
It's all in my lifeline, my love life, it's in my hand
でもない こうでもないな 寂しい寂しいノンセンスDAY
Lonely, a lonely, nonsensical DAY
いっそ密会ラフに 節操無い解：LOVE ME
Rough love in secret, my not-safe-for-work goodbye
溺れ奴隷 踊れ踊れ 亡霊だ
Obsessive actions, my dancing, putrefaction, ah
なにもない なにもない 私なにもない ねぇ
Nothing at all, nothing at all / Get it? I'm nothing at all
変われない 変われない 私変われない ねぇ
Won't change a bit, won't change a bit / Get it? I won't change a bit
分からない 分からない 「分かる」分からない
Don't understand, don't understand / Don't act like you understand
はい 目もと以外は 隠して
Ah, halfway covered my face pic with a hand
ダダダダダダダリダリダーリンダリ
Ah, da-da-da-da darling, dulling, darling! funny!
はい 冴えない愛情論でおねだり
Sure, I'll just keep pestering till you love me!
ダダダダダダダリ脳裏 dirty ＆ dirty
My da-da-da-da darling thinks I'm dirty, I'm dirty!
会いたい衝動 埋めてよ ダダ ダーリン
Please just finally notice me, my da-da-darling!
無い無い純情 感情が行ったり来たり
My impure emotions keep on coming and going
無い無い情緒感情でダダダ ダーリン
Petals lost and sappy feelings, da-da-darling!
寝転んゴロンでニャンニャン プリティプリティ ダイエットDAY
Prettily, prettily, dieting DAY
もう精一杯で詰み 暴論世界で無理
Relax and you'll be fine, I-my-me my whole life
病み悪化してんだって 承認承認 絶対だ
You say my symptoms are worse / It's love, you're losing your mind
なにもない なにもない 私なにもない ねぇ
Nothing at all, nothing at all
走れない 走れない 私走れない ねぇ
Won't change a bit, won't change a bit
分からない 分からない 「分かる」分からない
Don't understand, don't understand
はい 自撮りは全部 加工して
Ah, guess I'll photoshop it for instagram
ダダダダダダダリダリダーリンダリ
Ah, da-da-da-da darling, dulling, darling! funny!
はい 絶えない愛情論でさめたり
Sure, I guess that I'll stop being such a creep!
ダダダダダダダリ無理 dirty ＆ dirty
My da-da-da-da darling knows I'm dirty, I'm dirty!
会いたい衝動 止めてよ ダダ ダーリン
Please don't ever notice me, my da-da-darling!
踊れ 踊れ 叫べ 叫べ
I'm dancing, I'm screaming
踊れ 踊れ ルラパッパ
I'm dancing, ru rap papa
踊れ 踊れ 唄え 唄え
I'm dancing, I'm singing
踊れ 踊れ ルラパッパ
I'm dancing, ru rap papa
もどきん ドキン の しんどきん ドキン の
My heart is beating now, It's gonna beat right out,
はい 素顔は全部 無くして
Ah, watch me disappear to an idol now
ダダダダダダダリダリダーリンダリ
Ah, da-da-da-da darling, dulling, darling! funny!
どうしようもない感情論に笑ったり
Sure, I'll laugh at all the feelings you show me
ダダダダダダダリ脳裏 dirty ＆ dirty
My da-da-da-da darling mind is dirty, a dummy
会いたい衝動 埋めてよ ダダ ダーリン
Don't wanna want you to see me, da-da-darling!
無い無い無い無い無い無い無い無い
Nah...
無い無い反応 返答を期待したり
Don't expect an answer to anything, no, nothing
無い無い無い無い無い無い無い無い
Nah...
無い無い妄想 感情でダダダ ダーリン
No delusions, sappy feelings, da-da-darling
無い無い情緒 感情でダダダ ダーリン
Petals lost and sappy feelings, da-da-darling
ねぇ ダーリン
Hey, darling!
けーたいみしてよ
Let me see your phone!
待ちわびている大通り
Waiting on the main street,
目眩しそうな人混み
in a dizzying crowd.
くるり回った昼下がり
A spinning afternoon,
立ち止まってるぼっぽ
stopping in your tracks, boppo.
しまいきれてない表情
An expression you can't quite hide,
どこ見てるのぼっぽ
where are you looking, boppo?
知らない 今何
I don't know, right now,
目と目とまった合図
eyes meeting, a stopping signal.
ロングのロリーズ
Long lollies,
あとでね 黒文字
"later on," in black text.
隠してもムダね
Even if you hide it, it's useless!
けーたいみしてよ 今から
Let me see your phone, right now!
ねえ 今から
Hey, right now,
ねえ いいでしょ けーたいみしてよ
hey, is that okay? Let me see your phone!
怯んでるの予想通り
Flinching, just as expected,
だって賭けたこの試み
because I bet on this attempt.
くるり回った昼下がり
A spinning afternoon,
立ち止まっていないで
don't just stand there,
怒ったりしないでよあいにく
don't get angry, unfortunately...
チゅチュチュチュ
Chu, chu, chu, chu!
いらない いらない
I don't need it, I don't need it!
使い古しの愛も
Even used-up love,
言い訳はだめ
excuses won't do!
画面じゃなくここ見て
Look here, not at the screen,
取り上げるからね
because I'm gonna take it away!
けーたいみしてよ 今から
Let me see your phone, right now!
ねえ 今から ねえ 今から
Hey, right now, hey, right now!
ねえ いいでしょ けーたいかしてよ
Hey, is that okay? Lend me your phone!
けーたいかしてよ 今から
Lend me your phone, right now!
ねえ 今すぐ 渡しなさい
Hey, right now, hand it over!
ねえ いいでしょ けーたいみしてよ
Hey, is that okay? Let me see your phone!
おお！やっと目が覚めたのか！
Oh! You're finally awake!
おはようございます！
Good morning!
よく眠れましたか？
Did you sleep well?
ここは…ここはどこ？
Here... Where is this?
ここはオリーの部屋だよ！
This is Ollie's room!
なんだって？
What was that?
ちょっと違って？
It looks a bit different?
えへへ～バレたか～
Ehehe~ You found out~
オリー、その…私たちのためだけに部屋を準備したんだよ！
Ollie, um... I prepared this room just for the two of us!
私たちの時間をできるだけ特別なものにしたいと思って…だから一生懸命頑張って、私たちのための完璧な景色を用意したんだ！
I wanted to make our time together as special as possible... So I worked really hard and prepared the perfect scenery just for us!
オリー、さらに君が寝ている間にわざわざここで運んできたんだよ。
Ollie even carried you here while you were asleep,
君が疲れ…疲れらないようにね～
just so you wouldn't get tired, you know~
オリーはせー愛すいつま君かと私は君のことが大好きでこの気持ちがちゃんと届いてほしいんだよ～
Ollie loves you so much, and I want my feelings to properly reach you~
どうしたの？
What's wrong?
…いつものオリーじゃない？
...Aren't you acting like your usual self?
えへへ～あなたってほんと～
Ehehe~ You're really something~
まったく何の話してるか分からないわ～
I have no idea what you're talking about~
あぁ！待って！
Ah! Wait!
行かないで！
Don't go!
ええ…そんなふうに逃げちゃうなんて信じられないよ～
Eh... I can't believe you'd run away like that~
でも、照れてる君、めちゃ可愛かった～！
But you being all shy and flustered was super cute~!
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die.
指切りげんまん ホラでも吹いたら
Pinky swear, if I do tell a lie,
針でもなんでも 飲ませていただきます
I'm willing to swallow needles or anything.
Monday It doesn't matter if it's Sunday
鏡よ鏡よ この世で1番
Mirror, mirror, the best in this world,
変わることのない 愛をくれるのは だれ
who will give me unchanging love?
No need to ask cause it's my darling
わたしの最後は あなたがいい
I want you to be my last,
あなたとこのまま おさらばするより
I'd rather hang out with you like this
死ぬのがいいわ 死ぬのがいいわ
than say goodbye... I'd rather die!
三度の飯より あんたがいいのよ
You're better than three meals a day.
あんたとかのまま おさらばするより
Shall I stay with you like this?
死ぬのがいいわ 死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die, I'd rather die!
それでも時々 浮つく My Heart 死んでも治りゃしねぇ
Still, sometimes my heart floats, even if I die I won't be cured—
直して見せます Baby Yeah I ain't nothin but ya baby
I'll show you I can fix it, baby! Yeah, I ain't nothin' but ya baby!
失って初めて気がつくなんて そんなダサいこともしたくないのよ Goodbye
You only realize it when you lose it, I don't want to do anything so lame, goodbye!
Oh don't you ever say byebye Ai yai yai
Oh, don't you ever say bye bye...
わたしの最後は あなたがいい
I want you to be my last,
あなたとこのまま おさらばするより
I'd rather hang out with you like this
死ぬのがいいわ 死ぬのがいいわ 死ぬのがいいわ
than say goodbye... I'd rather die!
三度の飯より あんたがいいのよ
You're better than three meals a day.
あんたとこのまま おさらばするよ
Shall I stay with you like this?
死ぬのがいいわ 死ぬのがいいわ 死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die, I'd rather die!
わたしの最後は あなたがいい
I want you to be my last,
あなたとこのまま おさらばするより
I'd rather hang out with you like this
死ぬのがいいわ 死ぬのがいいわ 死ぬのがいいわ
than say goodbye... I'd rather die!
三度の飯より あんたがいいのよ
You're better than three meals a day.
あんたとこのまま おさらばするよ
Shall I stay with you like this?
死ぬのがいいわ 死ぬのがいいわ 死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die, I'd rather die!
それでも時々 浮つく My Heart もう要らないのよ Bye bye
Still, sometimes my heart floats, I don't need anything so lame anymore, bye-bye!
I'll always stick wit ya my baby my baby
I'll always stick with ya, my baby...
ねぇアナタには見えない事ばかり アタシは見えている事を知らないの?
Hey, you don't see all the things that I can see, don't you know?
背中につけられた誰かのキッスの跡 一人じゃ買う訳の無い それも見て見ぬふりなのは
Someone's kiss mark left on your back, something I'd never buy alone—turning a blind eye to all of it...
なぜ 笑っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ
Why? A girlfriend so cute it makes you laugh!
常時奔放 狂気 短気 怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Wild, crazy, short-tempered, shouting until our eyes meet—a direct hit!
洗脳完了 女上手 愛してんのさ 強く愛してんのさ
Brainwashing complete, master manipulator! I love you so, I love you so deeply!
ねぇ精神から全身まで 表面から内面まで 脳天から先端まで知りたいの それから
Hey, from soul to body, surface to inside, head to toe, I want to know it all! And then...
最近聞いた音楽から 散財した総額まで 完全把握しないと気が済まないの
From the music you recently listened to, to how much you've spent—I won't be satisfied until I know everything!
とかく言ったって実際の問題は その眼中アタシ何割くらい担ってるか
No matter what you say, the real question is what percentage of your attention do I occupy?
隠してないで 確信を頂戴 さねど黙って語らず Bye-bye
Don't hide it, give me certainty! Yet staying silent without a word, bye-bye.
なぜ 困っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ 容姿端麗 艶美 甘美
Why? A girlfriend so cute it's troubling! Flawless, charming, sweet.
身勝手だって泣く シックな素振り 瞬時酩酊 女冥利 愛しちまうのさ されど愛しちまうのさ
Crying that she's selfish, chic demeanor, instantly drunk, a woman's true bliss—I end up loving you anyway!
過去を喰らう程にポップなエレジー 排気口から香るラーメン
A pop elegy so strong it devours the past, the scent of ramen from the exhaust vent.
騙し奪われる恋でもいいの だってこの恋は めちゃくちゃ可愛いんでしょ?
Even a deceived and stolen love is fine, because this love is insanely cute, right?
笑っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ 常時奔放 狂気 短気
A girlfriend so cute it makes you laugh! Wild, crazy, short-tempered.
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃 洗脳完了 女上手
Shouting until our eyes meet—a direct hit! Brainwashing complete, master manipulator!
困っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ 容姿端麗 艶美 甘美
A girlfriend so cute it's troubling! Flawless, charming, sweet.
身勝手だって泣く シックな素振り 瞬時酩酊 女冥利
Crying that she's selfish, chic demeanor, instantly drunk, a woman's true bliss—
愛しちまうのさ 強く愛しちまうのさ
I love you so, I love you so deeply!
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
The beginning of the night... Bunny Girl
誘惑される鼓動に
Lured in by the beating heart,
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
A toast to love amidst bursting conflicts,
伝えられなくても
Even if it can't be conveyed.
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
The beginning of love... Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って
Piercing through someone,
澄んだ君の目を孕んで
Embracing your clear eyes.
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Come on, carve out posh steps,
仕事帰りの疲れは
The fatigue of coming home from work
私と、このグラスに
With me, into this glass...
さあ 自分好みに縫って
Come on, tailored to your own liking,
世間に対する気持ち私に注いでみない?
Why don't you pour your feelings for the world into me?
ありがちなラブソングでも
Even in a clichéd love song,
愛が込められてるの
There is love packed inside,
それでも汚れるのね
Yet it still gets stained, doesn't it?
君を見れば分かるの
I can tell when I look at you.
下を向く君の目を
Your eyes looking down—
無理やり開こうとはしない
I won't try to force them open.
だからそんな顔せず手を差し伸べて ほら
So don't make that face, reach out your hand, look.
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
The beginning of the night... Bunny Girl
誘惑される鼓動に
Lured in by the beating heart,
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
A toast to love amidst bursting conflicts,
伝えられなくても
Even if it can't be conveyed.
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
The beginning of love... Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って
Piercing through someone,
澄んだ君の目を孕んで
Embracing your clear eyes.
君の愛を知った気でハイになっていて 感度去っていて 毎度泣いていてさ
Thinking I knew your love, getting high, sensitivity fading, crying every time,
それくらいでいいんでしょ
Well, that's enough, isn't it?
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Come on, carve out posh steps,
君の顔色今ではマシになってきてるから
Your complexion is getting better now, isn't it?
君に委ねるわ Bunny Girl
I leave it to you... Bunny Girl,
私をあげるわ Bunny Girl
I give myself to you... Bunny Girl,
誘惑される鼓動に
Lured in by the beating heart,
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
A toast to love amidst bursting conflicts,
伝えられてるはず
It should be conveyed.
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
The beginning of the night... Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って
Piercing through someone,
澄んだ君の目を孕んで
Embracing your clear eyes.
Berry you are!
There you are!
Akhirnya ketemu juga! Dari tadi aku cariin kamu tahu!
I was looking everywhere for you!
Kamu nggak bilang kalau kita bakal main petak umpet~
You didn't tell me we were playing hide-and-seek~
Ternyata kamu ada di neon stage, ya!
Well, I see you made it to my neon stage, ya!
Jadi gimana? Cantik nggak neon stagenya? Kan?
How do you like it? It's really pretty, right?
Ollie yang siapin, nih! Keren kan, neonnya banyak banget!
I put a lot of effort into it!
Pas kamu lagi sembunyi tadi, Ollie juga ganti baju,
And while you were hiding, I had the time to change my clothes!
Loh, imut nggak~? Ollie, megah & kyut nggak, ya~?
Don't I look super cute?
Hehe~ Sebenarnya masih banyak yang Ollie siapin buat kamu~
Yeah, and I still have a lot that I prepared for you,
Jadi kita udahan ya main petak umpetnya~
so I hope that we can put a rest to this hide-and-seek~
Hah? Nggak mau?
Huh? No?
Eh, kamu, tuh... Sejak sampe di sini, tingkah kamu aneh banget, deh...
Hey, you've been acting...
Sejak sampe di sini, tingkah kamu aneh banget, deh...
Really weird. Ever since you got here, and...
Ollie nggak ngerti...
I just don't understand...
Padahal dari kemarin kamu caper ke Ollie, sampe nge-like sama nge-comment di semua posnya Ollie...
Even though since yesterday you've been trying to get my attention, liking and commenting on all my posts...
Bukanya ini yang kamu mau?
Isn't this what you wanted?
Kamu sayang Ollie, kan?
You love Ollie, don't you?
Kamu nggak mau ngabisin waktu sama Ollie?
Don't you want to spend more time with me?
Kok kamu tidak menerima perasaan Ollie, sih?
Why aren't you accepting my feelings?
Seharusnya kamu seneng, tapi... tingkah kamu aneh...
You're supposed to be happy, but... your behavior is so strange...
Eh! Bentar! Tyo! Tyo! Hei, wait!
Eh! Wait! Wh-What?! Hey, wait!
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service shutdown is really hitting me, meow.
どんだけ泣いたかわかんないや
I don't know how much I've cried...
つら　さこりっぱ
It hurts, so lonely.
ぽっかり空いて埋まらないやいや
A gaping hole that won't fill up,
ほしいラブぴったん
I want some love.
中途半端な出会いじゃ刺さないやいや
Half-hearted encounters won't pierce me.
やっぱり無理かもばたんきゅー
Guess it's no use, good night.
ぜっそりハートが直んないやいや
This broken heart won't fix itself,
出してよすぐ処方箋
write me a prescription right now!
サヨナラのトゲなんで抜けないの
Why won't this thorn of goodbye come out?
きみの代わりの人型が全然見つからない
I can't find a replacement for you anywhere.
サッドガール・セックスぱぱんうぶの出棺
Sad girl sex, the send-off of innocence.
きっとどんな想いだけれド誰かと寝ても寂しさが発火
No matter what feelings I had, sleeping with someone else just ignites my loneliness.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service shutdown is really hitting me, meow.
サッドガール・セックスぱぱんラブの接待きっとまた会えるなんてさあ
Sad girl sex, love's hospitality. As if we'll surely meet again.
思い出のきみに食い殺されこ
Eaten alive by the you in my memories.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service shutdown is really hitting me, meow.
ねえマンガ返してよ最新話のあのキャラ死んじゃったよ
Hey, give me back my manga! That character died in the latest chapter!
教えてくれたバンドメンバーがクスリで捕まっちゃったよ
The band member you told me about got busted for drugs!
一緒にいたこと消えないやいや全部が二人だった
The time we spent together won't fade away, everything was about the two of us.
きっときみは今誰かといるのあたしだけが課金中
You're probably with someone else right now, while I'm the only one paying to play.
サッドガール・セックスぱぱんうぶの出棺嫉妬ずらくてえんぱってら
Sad girl sex, send-off of innocence, envious and empathetic.
上書きがしたいどうしてくれないの
I want to overwrite it, why won't you let me?
愛のガチャガチャ天井はない
There's no pity system for the gacha of love.
サッドガール・セックスぱぱんラブのバッシュちょっとエグすぎないほんとさ
Sad girl sex, love's bash, isn't this a bit too brutal, really?
涙の跡に狂気が走った
Madness surged in the traces of my tears.
愛のガチャガチャ天井はない
There's no pity system for the gacha of love.
もしもしが叶う素敵世界ならばきみはサヨナラ取り下げを検討加速しちゃう？
In a wonderful world where "hello" comes true, would you accelerate considering withdrawing your goodbye?
サッドガール・セックスぱぱんうぶの出棺なんでこんな終わってんだろ
Sad girl sex, send-off of innocence, why has it ended up like this?
誰かとねたら埋められるようなレベルの愛だ
That's the level of love that gets filled if you sleep with someone else.
そんなんじゃない！
It's not like that!
サッドガール・セックスぱぱんラブでぺちゃんこ今でも想ってんのは期待よりの地獄もう戻れないの
Sad girl sex, crushed by love, what I'm still thinking of is a hell worse than expectations, we can't go back anymore.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service shutdown is really hitting me, meow.
探せ続行だめだめ波乱
Search, continue, no-no turbulence.
揺らせ絶頂あせあせ弾
Rock the climax, sweating bullets.
探せ続行だめだめ波乱
Search, continue, no-no turbulence.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service shutdown is really hitting me, meow.
檻の中あたしの愛猫お帰りなさい君にニャオ
Inside the cage, my beloved cat. Welcome back, meow to you.
お帰りなさい君にニャオ悪い子ね怪我したお身体で
Welcome back, meow to you. Bad child, with your injured body.
行きはよいで帰りは怖い愛を知らない飽き猫さん
The way there is easy, the way back is scary, bored cat who doesn't know love.
間抜けな愛嬌とかそりゃ結構睨めっこほらバレバレで
Silly charm and all that is fine, staring contest, look, it's totally obvious.
なんできみお仕置きだ自己嫌悪
Why are you getting punished? Self-loathing.
君はあたしだけの愛猫だからだんだん好きになり
You are my only beloved cat, so I'm gradually growing to love you.
好きになる
Falling in love...
ねぇ 愛して
Hey, love me...
ドンドン 好きになる
Falling deeper in love...
好きになる ねぇ 愛して
Falling in love, hey, love me...
可愛いね 首輪をつけて
How cute, put a collar on me.
大切にめでて あげるにゃお
I'll cherish and adore you, meow.
檻の中の子猫ちゃん
A kitten inside a cage,
愛の乱数をさあ 踊りましょう
Let's dance to random bursts of love.
喉鳴らし尻尾揺おで ほらどうぞ
Purring, wagging tails, here you go.
睨めっこ あら甘えん坊さん
Staring contest? Oh, you're a spoiled one.
そっぽ向いてもそれだけこ?
Even if you look away, is that all?
君はあたしだけの愛猫なの
You are my one and only beloved cat.
ドンドン 好きになる
Falling deeper in love...
好きになる ねぇ 愛して
Falling in love, hey, love me...
ドンドン 好きになる
Falling deeper in love...
好きになる ねぇ 愛して
Falling in love, hey, love me...
見けられない 癒されないのばっかしょの愛が死の愛して
Unseen, unsatiated, only dying love...
さあ 死んでだって君を 愛猫さん
Now, even if it kills you, my beloved cat.
Halooo? Kamu di mana?
Hellooo? Where are you?
ねぇ、どこにいるの?
Hey, where are you?
Ish, keluar, dong!
Ugh, come out already!
うぅ〜、出てきてよ！
Ugh~, come on out!
Katanya udahan main petak umpetnya?
I thought we were done playing hide-and-seek?
かくれんぼはもう終わりだと思ったのに…
I thought we were done playing hide-and-seek...
Kamu ke mana coba...
Where could you possibly be...
もぉ〜、どこに隠れているの?
Moo~, where are you hiding?
Ayo tunjukin dirimu!
Show yourself!
早く出てきて！ Beneran deh, ngasih kerjaan aja kamu...
Come out quickly! Seriously, you're giving me so much work...
Ketemu!
Found you!
あはは！見つけたよ！
Ahaha! Found you!
Jangan ke mana-mana lagi, ya~! 今度はどこにも行かないでよ～！
Don't go anywhere else now~!
ほとはしげく香る君のその髪が
The profusely fragrant hair of yours
僕の心を踊らせたんです
made my heart dance.
頷くだけ 今は それだけで
Just nodding, for now, is enough
この身屈めますから
to humble this body.
Midnight光線Darling
Midnight ray, Darling.
堪えきれぬ欲望に任せて
Yielding to unbearable desire,
Midnight光線Darling
Midnight ray, Darling.
僕に仕える気になったら
if you feel like serving me.
願いは三度の絶頂を
My wish is for a triple climax
胸の中で至る
reaching its peak within my chest.
今宵も僕らは繁栄の
Tonight, too, for our prosperity,
ために愛を放つ
we unleash our love.
抗いの呟きは裏腹に
Contrary to defiant whispers,
身体は嬉しそうに動いたんです
my body moved as if overjoyed.
この翼に輪を付けるかは
Whether to put a ring on these wings
僕ら次第ですから
is up to us, so
真面目ですかな
are you being earnest?
淫らですかな
Or are you being lewd?
Midnight光線Darling
Midnight ray, Darling.
愛と欲に純白を求めて
Seeking purity in love and desire,
Midnight光線Darling
Midnight ray, Darling.
僕を拒む気になっても
even if you decide to reject me.
願いは三度の絶頂を
My wish is for a triple climax
胸の中で至る
reaching its peak within my chest.
零れる涙が飽和して
Overflowing tears reach saturation,
僕は今に果てる
and I perish now.
その溢れた吐息の原因なんだって?
What could be the cause of those overflowing sighs?
よろめく恐怖が原因なんだって?
What could be the cause of that staggering fear?
それでも君ならいいんだって
Even so, you'd be fine,
さらに
and even more...
願いは三度の絶頂を
My wish is for a triple climax
胸の中で至る
reaching its peak within my chest.
今宵も僕らは繁栄の
Tonight, too, for our prosperity...
ねえ あたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know all about it...
きみがひとり “涙”してるの 知ってるよ
You're all alone, shedding tears in secret.
グスン グスン 凹んでさ 弱音 ヒトカラ in the night
Drowning in your sighs all through the night.
ねえ いいでしょう？ 舐め取って 飲み干したいんだってば
Come on, let me swallow your tears and dry them up.
もういいでしょ そうそう、あたしがきみに尽くしてあげてるのに
Because I'm here to give you my all.
ねえ あたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know all about it...
きみがひとり “涙”してるの 知ってるよ
You're all alone, shedding tears in secret.
グスン グスン 凹んでさ 弱音 ヒトカラ in the night
Drowning in your sighs all through the night.
ねえ いいでしょう？ 舐め取って 飲み干したいんだってば
Come on, let me swallow your tears and dry them up.
ねえ 泣いたっていいよ
It's okay to cry now.
ねえ あたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know all about it...
きみがひとり “涙”してるの 知ってるよ
You're all alone, shedding tears in secret.
グスン グスン 凹んでさ 弱音 ヒトカラ in the night
Drowning in your sighs all through the night.
ねえ いいでしょう？ 舐め取って 飲み干したいんだってば
Come on, let me swallow your tears and dry them up.
mwah！ お願い きみが欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad.
慰めさせて シェイク シェイク 愛の才能で
Let me soothe you with the talent of love!
泣いてくれなきゃ 濡れてしまう 濡れていたいいでしょ？
Cry for me, let your tears overflow and soak me.
舐め取って 飲み干したいんだってば
Suck them dry, I want to drink them all up!
mwah！ お願い きみが欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad.
頼り散らして シックラブ なんて最高ね
Laugh it off, hop, step, jump, and let's go!
わけないきゅんの“痛い” 感じていたいんでしょ？
Share it with me, it's too heavy for you to bear alone.
吸い取って 救いたいんだってば
Let me absorb it and save you!
見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい
I want to see... I want to see...
見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい きみの中
I want to see inside of you.
ねえ あたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know all about it...
きみがひとり悔しがってるの 知ってるよ
You're regretting something all by yourself.
グスン グスン 凹んでさ 弱音 ヒトカラ in the night
Drowning in your sighs all through the night.
ねえ あたし知ってるよ きみはできる子
Hey, I know you can do it.
辛いときは 弱いくらいでちょうどいい あたしそれでも好きだよ
Even when you're weak, I still love you.
mwah！ お願い きみが欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad.
名前呼んでよ いつだって会い参上
Call my name, I'll come running anytime!
きみはひとりだ だから歌う“ひとりじゃない”
You're not alone anymore!
もういいでしょ ソロプレイはおしまいなんだってば
No more solo play!
きみが病めるときも あたしそばにいるわ
Whenever you're feeling down, I'm right by your side.
いつも見守っているわ そうよ怖くないのよ
I'm always watching over you, so don't be afraid.
mwah！ お願い きみが欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad.
慰めさせて シェイク シェイク 愛の才能で
Let me soothe you with the talent of love!
泣いてくれなきゃ 濡れてしまう 濡れていたいいでしょ？
Cry for me, let your tears overflow and soak me.
舐め取って 飲み干したいんだってば
Suck them dry, I want to drink them all up!
mwah！ お願い きみが欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad.
頼り散らして シックラブ なんて最高ね
Laugh it off, hop, step, jump, and let's go!
わけないきゅんの“痛い” 感じていたいんでしょ？
Share it with me, it's too heavy for you to bear alone.
吸い取って 救いたいんだってば
Let me absorb it and save you!
ねえ あたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know all about it...
きみがひとり “涙”してるの 知ってるよ
You're all alone, shedding tears in secret.
グスン グスン 凹んでさ 弱音 ヒトカラ in the night
Drowning in your sighs all through the night.
朝が来るまで 一緒コース もっと泣いたって 何だって受け止めてあげる
Let's talk all night 'til the sun comes up.
もう我慢しないで 出して出しちゃったってば
No more holding back, let it all out!
ふうっ！ やっと終わった！
Fiuh! Finally done!
これで、もう逃げ出したりしないからね～
This way, you won't be running away anymore.
いい子にしてじっとしててね～？
Now be a good boy and sit tight, okay?
本当に汗ほどだい働いちゃったわ！
Honestly, you really made me work up a sweat!
あなたを探して追いかけ回しちゃった～
Making me look for you and chase you down.
やっとまた一緒にいられて嬉しいよ～
But I'm just glad that we're finally together again.
今度こそ二人で一緒に過ごせるんだ～！！
Now we get to spend some time together, just the two of us!
ねぇ、おい。こっちを見ろよ…
Hey, hey. Pay attention and look at me.
ふっ、がいい子。いい子いい子〜
That's a good boy.
さて、皆さんの注意を引けたところでついに私がずっと取り組んできたものをお見せできます！これをみてください！やった！
Now that I have your attention, I can finally show you what I've been working on all this time! Check this out! Yay!
今回も誕生日グッズが出ます！
This time, it's a birthday merchandise line-up!
今回はグッズが出ます！オリーが紹介する一つずつね！
I'll introduce them one by one, okay?
はい！じゃあ最初のアイテムは…こちらー！
Alright, now the first item will be... this!
うわー！それはワイドラバーマット！
Whoa, it's a wide rubber mat!
いーんですっごく可愛いー！
Isn't it so cute?
Wherever you're gaming,
you always remember me.
The cement kind of looks like a yonder, doesn't it?
The cement kind of looks like a yandere, doesn't it?
But I'm not a yonder, I'm just your girlfriend.
But I'm not a yandere, I'm just your girlfriend.
Yeah, it's wide, slightly large-sized rubber mat recommended for everyday use,
Yeah, a wide, slightly large-sized rubber mat recommended for everyday use,
and the illustration is by Hanakusa Akira-sensei! Arigatou gozaimasu!
and the illustration is by Hanakusa Akira-sensei! Thank you very much!
Okay, then the next item will be, koti-ra!
Okay, then the next item will be, right here!
Wow, it's a pillow! Isn't it so cute?
So that when you're sleeping, you remember me, you dream of me.
So that when you're sleeping, you can remember me, and dream of me.
This it looks so fluffy, so you guys better get it for a good night's sleep!
This looks so fluffy, so you guys better get it for a good night's sleep!
Right? And followed by koti-ra!
Right? And followed by right here!
It's a ring necklace!
Well, it's a ring, if it doesn't fit your size, then you can just wear it as a necklace,
Well, it's a ring, but if it doesn't fit your size, you can wear it as a necklace!
isn't that really cool? Sore kore wa ne, yubiwa demo, demo, koresize ga attenai nara, necklace demo tsukairu...
Isn't that really cool? So if it doesn't fit your size, you can use it as a necklace!
So make sure that when you get up, you wear this so that whenever you go grocery shopping, no other girls out there will be hitting on you!
So make sure that when you get up, you wear this so no other girls hit on you!
Right? And then we also have koti-ra!
Right? And then we also have right here!
It's a mug! Isn't it so cute?
I really like the design, so not only when you're working or gaming, or grocery shopping, or sleeping, but even when you're drinking, you think of me.
I really like the design, so use it anytime, and even when drinking, think of me.
And of course, not forgetting koti-ra!
And of course, not forgetting right here!
Situational voice packs in three languages: in Nihongo, in Bahasa Indonesia, and in English!
Situational voice packs in three languages: Nihongo, Bahasa Indonesia, and English!
Soshite saigo ni for the set, koni taidai kata ni wa, suuryou gentei de ziki-hitsu, san-iri, check, bromide card ga suite kimasu!
And for the set, limited edition autographed photo-style cards are included!
And for those of you guys who buy the full set, oh there will be limited edition postcard with my message and my sign, yeah!
And for the full set, there will be a postcard with my message and sign!
For those of you guys who buy like the normal version, you guys can also get the postcard with my sign and message! Yang beli versi biasa juga akan dapat postcard yang ada message dan sign ya!
And for those who buy the normal version, you can get the postcard too!
Okay, that is all. That was a mouthful, wasn't it?
Tapi kamu pasti beli merch Ollie, kan-?
But you'll buy my merch, won't you?
That's what I like to do!
Wish I could spend more time with you, but fortunately, our time is limited, damn.
Wish I could spend more time with you, but our time is limited, damn.
Tapi sebelum itu, Ollie masih ada hadiah buat kamu! Jadi tolong dengarkan ya~
I have one last gift for you, so please pay attention and wait for me!
ゾッとした表情が可愛いね
That horrified look on your face is so cute.
君のその身体が欲しいの
I want that body of yours.
Love it? ナニにラリって
Love it? What are you tripping on?
愛 high 可哀想ね 君は悪い子なの
Love high, poor thing, you're such a bad boy.
どの娘がお好きで? 散々に
Which girl do you like best? Scattered around,
色目が上手で 頭湧き
flirting skillfully, losing your mind.
君に踊らされちゃって
Being made to dance by you,
アタシは狂う What is love it?
I'm going crazy. What is love it?
君の血肉まで 骨の髄まで
Down to your flesh and blood, down to your marrow,
挿れて空っぽになる 愛のパペット
inserting until empty, a puppet of love.
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
Your chest hurts, your breath is choking,
それが恋と教えてあげるわ
I'll teach you that's love.
虚ろな声で ほら囁いて
With a hollow voice, come on, whisper,
いい子ね首輪付けた 君はLove it
good boy, wearing a collar, you're love it.
イカれちゃった? noね 恋は盲目ね
Are you crazy? No, love is blind.
したいよねしてあげるわ 逝って?
You want to? I'll do it for you. Going?
濡れて 君の赤い生生 溺れるまで
Get wet, in your raw red blood, until you drown.
イタイイタイノドンデユケ 死んで膿むまで
It hurts, it hurts, go away, until you die and fester.
愚かめ 愚かめ まぬけな顔して
Foolish, foolish, making such a foolish face,
君は悪い子なの？
Are you a bad child?
痛いのが好きで さにざに
Liking the pain, sanizani,
あらう口はチャックで
Zip up your washing mouth,
何？ 何？
What? What?
性に踊らされちゃう 君を喰らう
I'll devour you, made to dance by nature...
君の中まで 骨の髄まで
Right down into you, down to your bone marrow,
しゃぶりつくせば もう空っぽの
If I suck you dry, you'll be empty,
胸が苦しいね
Your chest hurts so much,
息が詰まるのね
Your breath is choking,
それが恋と教えてあげる
I'll teach you that this is love.
君はピエロね 愛を囁いて
You're a pierrot, whispering of love,
人間の形した君はラベ
You in human form are...
イカれちゃったね 恋は盲目ね
You've gone crazy, love is blind,
したいよねしてあげる会いて...
You want it, I'll give it to you, meeting...
むさぼり尽くす汚れたちに溺れるまで
Until we drown in all our greed and filth,
痛い痛いな どん底 雪 息が止まるまで
Painful, painful rock bottom until breath stops,
むさぼり尽くす汚れたちに溺れるまで
Until we drown in all our greed and filth,
痛い痛いな どん底 雪 息が止まるまで
Painful, painful rock bottom until breath stops,
Thank you so much for coming to watch this 3D birthday live!
How was it? Did you feel my love?
Oh, look at that! It's the specially prepared bedroom! Cute, isn't it?
It has a bed, a sofa, Udin... And I don't know if you noticed, but...
There was a display photo of the people I cherish the most in there! Did you catch it?
I think the neon stage was really cool, too!
You probably spotted a bunch of TVs sitting around.
And well, those are there to help me watch you from afar~!
Cool, right?
Uh, but come to think of it, I really did drag you around the stages, huh?
Um, how are you? Do you feel sick? Are you okay? You're not tired?
I'm a bit worried, but I think it shouldn't affect you too much since I carried you while you were still sleeping...
Ha? What? Ngga' - koki? Ollie nggak ngomong apa-apa! Ah, sou ieba!
Huh? What? No, koki? Ollie didn't say anything! Ah, come to think of it!
Eh, speaking of you, you kept running and hiding away from me!
Naughty, naughty! Task - kask!
You always leave comments and likes on every post I make, so I thought you'd like it if I came to visit!
I didn't think you would actually surprise you that much.
I think maybe it was because you were too surprised when I suddenly appeared in front of you?
Yeah... But, just so you know, I worked really hard, just for you!
I practiced my singing, I sang a lot, and changed my outfit so many times!
And I wonder if my feelings reached you...
It obviously did, right?
Also, at the end, I finally managed to catch you!
That's what you hoped for, right? I mean, cuz you were running away from me...
...because you love me a lot! Obviously you were expecting it too, right?
Period! Anyways...
For those of you who are still watching — thank you by the way — I have an announcement!
I'll be featured in SO87's song, Love Me Back, complete with the music video!
It's going to be so cool, so keep an eye out, okay? Mm-hmm!
Ah, it's just so exciting, isn't it?
If you ever feel the need to feel my love again, then don't hesitate and please come back to watch the 3D Birthday Live again, okay?
I'll always be here waiting for you.
Anyways, Bye-bye! Otsucrazy~!
Crazyになるほど恋してる ZOMBIE
A ZOMBIE so in love she's going crazy